Guide to the Peter Storey papers, 1950-2014 RL.01260
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Peter Storey papers
1950-2014
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Storey, Peter John, 1938-
RL.01260
9 Linear Feet
11.9 Gigabytes
South African Methodist Church leader and anti-apartheid activist. The Peter Storey Papers contain correspondence, datebooks, articles, lectures, sermons, committee and subject files, clippings, scrapbooks, videotapes, and electronic records. The collection documents Peter Storey's leadership and active involvement in the Methodist Church of Southern Africa, the South African Council of Churches, the Central Methodist Mission in Johannesburg, the Truth and Reconciliation Commission, Gun Free South Africa, and other religious and anti-apartheid groups. Major subjects include Nelson Mandela, Winnie Mandela, urban ministry, crisis intervention, and political violence and elections in South Africa. Materials range in date from circa 1950 to 2006. Acquired as part of the Human Rights Archive.
5000 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
In addition, original audiovisual materials are closed to patron use. Technical Services staff need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Peter Storey papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2006.
Biographical Note
Peter Storey (b. 1938) was schooled in Cape Town, South Africa, spent some time in the South African Navy, and then trained for the Methodist ministry at Rhodes University. Storey pastored churches in Cape Town, and later served as a chaplain to Robben Island prison, where he ministered to Nelson Mandela. After two years in Australia, Storey returned to District Six, a coloured community in Cape Town whose people faced forced removal under apartheid law. Storey was prominent in the fight against these removals, at the same time launching a number of ministries, including The Carpenter's House, Cape Town's first non-racial community center, and founded Dimension, the national newspaper of the Methodist Church, which took an uncompromising anti-apartheid stance under his nine-year editorship.
He was appointed to Johannesburg's Central Methodist Church in 1976, the year of the Soweto uprising, and immediately questioned the all-white nature of the congregation. The following years saw the loss of some 200 white members, but also the creation of the first fully integrated Methodist church in the land. The Central Methodist Mission--as it became known--was a center of protest action against apartheid, often being surrounded and sometimes invaded by government Security Forces.
During this period Storey became Vice President of the South African Council of Churches (SACC) and was elected President of this body in 1981. In this position, he and Bishop Desmond Tutu, who was then General Secretary, steered the SACC through its most controversial and embattled era of anti-apartheid action. This included facing the notorious Eloff Commission of Inquiry into the SACC. His testimony to the Commission has been published under the title Here We Stand.
In 1984 Storey was elected President of the Methodist Church and co-lead an ecumenical delegation to the United Nations and Europe to urge international pressure against the South African Government's forced removal policy. He then became Bishop of the Central District, including Johannesburg and Soweto. He also headed up the Journey to the New Land transformation process, which has redesigned the Methodist Church for its mission in the new South Africa.
Committed to peacemaking, he co-chaired the Wits-Vaal Peace Secretariat, responsible for keeping the peace in the Johannesburg region in the run-up to the first democratic elections and became Patron of the Methodist Order of Peacemakers, which focused on non-violence. He was first chairperson of the Gunfree South Africa movement, and he was a member of President Mandela's Selection Committee for the Truth and Reconciliation Commission.
Storey has received honorary Doctor of Divinity and Doctor of Law degrees. His international ministry has included frequent preaching and lecturing journeys to the United States, Europe, and Australia, and he has addressed many conferences related to the situation in South Africa, the truth and reconciliation process, and world peace.
[Biographical Note adapted from: February 11, 1999 - Rev. Dr. Peter Storey at STH. Boston University School of Theology, March 24, 2003. http://www.bu.edu/sth/news/archive/storey.html]
Collection Overview
The Peter Storey Papers contain correspondence, datebooks, articles, lectures, sermons, committee and subject files, clippings, scrapbooks, videotapes, and electronic records. The collection documents Peter Storey's leadership and active involvement in the Methodist Church of Southern Africa, the South African Council of Churches, the Central Methodist Mission in Johannesburg, the Truth and Reconciliation Commission, Gun Free South Africa, and other religious and anti-apartheid groups. Major subjects include Nelson Mandela, Winnie Mandela, urban ministry, crisis intervention, and political violence and elections in South Africa. Materials range in date from circa 1950 to 2014. Acquired as part of the Human Rights Archive.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection contains electronic records that must be requested and accessed in our reading room. Contact Research Services with questions.
Conditions Governing Access
In accordance with the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 as amended, Duke University permits students to inspect their education records and limits the disclosure of personally identifiable information from education records. Contact Research Services for more information.
Apartheid -- South Africa; Human Rights -- South Africa; South Africa -- Race relations; South Africa -- Politics and government -- 20th century; Machine-readable records; Videocassettes; Clippings (information artifacts); South African Council of Churches; Storey, Peter John, 1938-; Mandela, Winnie; Methodist Church -- South Africa; Methodist Church of Southern Africa; South Africa. Truth and Reconciliation Commission; Gun Free South Africa (Organization); Human Rights Archive (Duke University); Mandela, Nelson, 1918-
- Correspondence, 1971-1997 and undated, 1.5 boxes
  - Correspondence, 1971-1985, 14 folders (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1985-1989, 6 folders (Box 1A)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1997 and undated (Box 2)
- Datebooks, 1963-1996, 3 boxes
  - Datebooks, 1963-1972, 10 items (Box 3)
  - Datebooks, 1973-1984, 12 items (Box 4)
  - Datebooks, 1985-1990, 6 items (Box 5)
  - Datebooks, 1991-1996, 6 items (Box 6)
- Subject files, circa 1970-2006 and undated, 6.5 boxes
  - Winnie Mandela saga, 1989-1998, 8 folders (Box 2)
  - Soweto Happenings, 1976-1978 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 2)
  - South African Council of Churches (SACC) Ecunews, 1979-1988 (Box 2)
  - God & Caesar material (Box 7)
  - Central Methodist Mission (CMM) quarterly meetings, 1976-1991 (Box 7)
  - Central Methodist Mission Leaders meetings, 1976-1991 (Box 7)
  - Central Methodist Mission staff meetings, 1990 (Box 7)
  - P. W. Botha trial, 1996-1998 (Box 8)
  - Truth and Reconciliation Commission, 1993-1998 (Box 8)
  - Gun Free South Africa, 1992-2001 and undated (Box 8)
  - Lectures on South Africa (Box 9)
  - Evangelism and Bible studies (Box 9)
  - John Wesley -- Methodism (Box 9)
  - National Peace Accord -- Elections (Box 9)
  - Race (Box 9)
  - City Ministry (Box 9)
  - Linda W. Kiester interview, 1986-1987 (Box 9)
  - Kiester notes: Packet 1.1-1.3 (Box 9)
  - Kiester notes: Packet 2.1-2.2 (Box 9)
  - Kiester notes: Packet 2.3 (Box 9)
  - Miscellaneous interviews (Box 9)
  - Peace, Non-Violent, 3 Folders (Box 10)
  - Preaching, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Addresses and Articles, 1970-1989, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Addresses and Articles, 1990-1997, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - CMM Staff Meetings, 1976-1984, Folders 1-2 of 3 (Box 10)
  - CMM Staff Meetings, 1976-1984, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 11)
  - South African Council of Churches (SACC) Presidium, 1976-1981, 3 folders (Box 11)
  - SACC, Rees, June 16, Other, ELOFF (Box 11)
  - SACC Finance, 1977-1980, 3 folders (Box 11)
  - Addresses on South Africa (Box 11)
  - Misc. Articles, Conferences, Notes (Box 12)
  - SACC Exec, 1975-1980, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - SACC Exec, 1981-1990s, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Unfiled SAAC (not on CDs) (Box 12)
  - Not on CDs (Box 12)
  - Addresses and Articles, 1998-2006, 3 folders (Box 12)
- Clippings, 1970-2003, 6.5 boxes
  - Press clippings (Box 11)
  - Press clippings, 1950-2003 (Box 13)
  - Winnie Mandela clippings (Box 13)
  - Photocopies of newspaper clippings (Box 14)
  - Scrapbook, 1979 (Box 14)
  - Scrapbook, 1980-1984 (Box 14)
  - Photocopies of newspaper clippings (Box 15)
- Videocassettes, circa 1995-2004 and undated, 2 boxes
  - 'This we can do for justice and for peace' - Tutu & Storey (Box 16)
  - PJS Speaks on TRC in Minneapolis, 1994 (Box 16)
  - 'The Peacemakers' - One day in the life of South Africa's Peace Accord (Box 16)
  - National Peace Accord Peace Song Compilation (Box 16)
  - Talking about God - Where is God in your life? (Box 16)
  - 'Healing the Memories' (USA) Central District Synod, July 1999 (Box 16)
  - When Love Takes You Prisoner Peter Storey - Pasadena, April 29, 2000 (Box 16)
  - Holy Communion - "God's Wholeness for a Broken World" Western North Carolina Conference, 1998 (Box 16)
  - Friday Morning Worship - "Relentless Hospitality of the Holy Spirit" Western North Carolina Conference, 1998 (Box 16)
  - Saturday Morning Worship - "God's Gift of Newness for us All" Western North Carolina Conference, 1998 (Box 16)
  - Discipline-Making Congregations Nashville, 2001 (Box 17)
  - PJS Farewells, SABC i/vs, TRC Willie Mandela Hearing (Box 17)
  - Elections, PJS on Tope Level, Mandela victory speech (Box 17)
  - Gospel Truth and Power - The Church as an Alternative Community University United Methodist Church, February 21, 2003 (Box 17)
  - Sermon by Rev. Dr. Peter Storey University United Methodist Church, February 22, 2003 (Box 17)
  - Lecture 1: "God's Power to Speak the Truth," October 11, 1998 "Gospel Truth and Power" - MTSO Schooler Lectures, 1997 (Box 17)
  - Lecture 2: "Speaking God's Truth to Power," October 12, 1998 "Gospel Truth and Power" - MTSO Schooler Lectures, 1997 (Box 17)
  - The Way of The Powerless Jesus, October 13, 1998 - MTSO Schooler Institute Worship Service, 1997 (Box 17)
  - Resistance & Reconciliation - The Church's Ecumenical Role in Ending Apartheid. The Kathleen & John F. Bricker Memorial Lecture, March 16, 1999 (Box 17)
- Electronic records, 1963-2014
  Scope and Contents note
  Series includes of data CDs containing scanned versions of documents found in the Correspondence and Subject Files Series of the Peter Storey Papers. The contents of each disk have been transferred to an archival storage server. The majority of the files are Portable Document Format (PDF), with few JPG and other formats present. Disks 19 and 20 of 21 were not received. A complete list of the file names and directory structure of the disks is available for reference.
  Also included are files extracted from a USB thumb drive, covering courses Storey taught for the Duke Divinity School, documents from Storey's work with the Seth Mokitimi Methodist Seminary (SMMS), writings, and some scanned material, as well as correspondence in both email and word processing formats.
  - Disk Label: CMM Staff minutes; Central Circuit quarterly min. 1976-1991; Central MM Staff meetings 1976-1989; CMM leaders minutes 1976-1991; Articles & Conferences Notes 1959-1997; NPA - Elections; PJS Addresses & Articles 1970-1989; PJS Addresses & Articles since 23001 (this should read: 1990-May 2000); Prayers by PJ Storey; Preaching, 2001-2002; 14 files; approximately 675 megabytes. (Disk 1, Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0003)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes document files in PDF format.
  - Disk Label: ORIGINAL; Articles from Sunday Independent; First Alan Walker lecture; Ministry and Issues; Protest and Resistance; Remembering SA; Sing the Lord's Song in Hostile Land; Things that Make for Peace; God and Caesar Reading Kit, 2002; 18 files; approximately 620 megabytes. (Disk 2, Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0003)
  - Disk Label: Bible Study(s), 2002; 1 file; approximately 375 megabytes. (Disk 3, Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0003)
    A document file in PDF format.
  - Disk Label: Peace (aaa01164); Evangelism; Peace and Non-violence (Damaged), 2002; 3 files; approximately 530 megabytes. (Disk 4, Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0003)
  - Disk Label: Poor, 2002; 1 file; approximately 650 megabytes. (Disk 6, Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0003)
    1 file; approximately 650 megabytes.
  - Disk Label: SACC 1982; Eloff Commission; JC Rees; R...; Venola; Naribia; Mokena; Race, 2002-2007; 2 files; approximately 660 megabytes. (Disk 7, Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0003)
  - Disk Label: City; SACC Exec meetings 1972-1980, 2 files; approximately 690 megabytes. (Disk 8, Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0003)
  - Disk Label: Praesidium; SACC 1977-1980; SACC Finance Committee 1978-1982, 2002; 2 files; approximately 670 megabytes. (Disk 9, Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0003)
  - Disk Label: June 16, 1976; Roelotse - Mokoena; SACC Exe Meetings 1981-1982 plus audits, 2002; 3 files; approximately 590 megabytes. (Disk 10, Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0003)
  - Disk Label: Asingeni - Chetty; Discussion on Wesley; Misc Interview et al (DAMAGED); Miscellaneous: Some Eloff PJS, Some SACC, Letter to PM, Meeting with Botha 1980, Invite to O...; Radio Talks July 1996; SACC Exec Meetings (DAMAGED), 5 files (Disk 11, Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0003)
    Conditions Governing Access note
    One file (SACC Exec meetings 1977-81.pdf) could not be transferred to the storage server.
  - Disk Label: JCR - PJS Resignation; SACC 1981; Wesley & Methodism, 2002; 3 files; approximately 690 megabytes. (Disk 12, Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0003)
  - Disk Label: GFSA, 2002; 138 files; approximately 75 megabytes. (Disk 13, Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0003)
  - Disk Label: Misc.; Interview part one, 2002; 1 file; approximately 590 megabytes. (Disk 14, Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0003)
    A document file in PDF format
  - Disk Label: Soweto; Misc.; Lectures on SA, 2003; 33 files; approximately 120 megabytes. (Disk 15, Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0003)
  - Disk Label: Truth and Reconciliation Commission; W. Mandela; Botha, 2003; 181 files; approximately 160 megabytes. (Disk 16, Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0003)
  - Disk Label: Correspondence, 1971-1987, 2002-2003; 599 files; approximately 650 megabytes. (Disk 17, Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0003)
  - Disk Label: Correspondence, 1988-1997 and undated, 2003; 238 files; approximately 210 megabytes. (Disk 18, Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0003)
  - Disk Label: Our Ancestors, 2003; 25 files; approximately 5 megabytes. (Disk 21, Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0003)
    Includes still image files in JPEG format.
  - 50th Wedding Anniversary, 2010-2014; 2 files; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
    Includes a still image file in JPEG format and a document file in MS Word format.
  - Bishop's Records PJS 1984-1997, 1963-1998; 87 files; approximately 5 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
    Includes document files in MS Word and Lotus WordPro formats. Dates taken from filenames rather than modified timestamps.
  - Charter for Compassion, 2009-2014; 18 files; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
    Includes document files in MS Word and PDF formats.
  - Clifford K Storey Material, 2012-2014; 12 files; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
    Includes document files in MS Word format.
  - Duke God and Caesar Course, 1999-2014; 199 files; approximately 20 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
    Primarily includes document files in MS Word, PowerPoint, and PDF formats.
  - Duke Pilgrimage, 2001-2014; 90 files; approximately 10 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
    Includes document files in MS Word, Excel, and PowerPoint formats.
  - Duke Related Matters, 2000-2011; 26 files; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
    Primarily includes document files in MS Word format.
  - Duke-MCSA Links, 2000-2007; 10 files; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - Greensboro TRC, 2002-2014; 7 files; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - Gunfree SA, 1996-2007; 56 files; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
    Includes document files in MS Word and plain text formats.
  - Life Line, 1996-2014; 11 files; approximately 5 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - Liturgies, 1996-2014; 119 files; approximately 5 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - My Addresses, 1996-2014; 194 files; approximately 10 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - My Articles, 1996-2014; 139 files; approximately 5 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
    Includes document files (MS Word and PDF formats) and still image files (JPEG format).
  - My Books and Material, 1998-2014; 288 files; approximately 25 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
    Primarily includes document files in MS Word and PDF formats.
  - My Diaries 1963 Onward, 2004-2014; 3 files; approximately 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - My Letters Received, 1998-2014; Approximately 350 files; approximately 30 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
    Includes document files in MS Word, PDF, plain text, and WordPro formats.
  - My Letters Sent, 1998-2014; 181 files; approximately 10 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - My Pictures, 2004-2014; 6 files; approximately 10 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
    Primarily includes still image files in JPEG format.
  - My Prayers, 2000-2011; 22 files; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - My Scans, 1981-2008; 11 files; approximately 5 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
    Includes still images files (JPEG format) and document files (MS Word format). Dates taken from filenames rather than the modified timestamp.
  - My Sermons, 1985-2014; 235 files; approximately 10 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
    Primarily includes document files in MS Word format. Dates taken from filenames rather than modified timestamp.
  - My Speaking Engagements, 2001-2014; 92 files; approximately 5 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
    Includes document files (MS Word format) and still image files (JPEG format).
  - Scanned Pics and Items, 2012-2014; 29 files; approximately 10 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - SMMS DOCUMENTS, 1998-2014; 638 files; approximately 850 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
    Includes document files (MS Word, PDF, MS PowerPoint, MS Excel, plain text, and RTF formats), still image files (JPEG format), and an audio file (MP3 format).
  - Wesley Studies, 2002-2014; 36 files; approximately 10 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - [Loose Files], 2002-2014; 5 files; approximately 210 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0001, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
    Includes document files in PDF and MS Word format.
  - Duke Local Church Course, 1998-2014; 322 files; approximately 50 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0002, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
    Conditions Governing Access
    FERPA information restricted until 2089.
    Primarily includes document files in MS Word, MS PowerPoint, and PDF formats.
  - Duke SA Field Placements, 2001-2014; 122 files; approximatley 25 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0002, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - Outlook email messages, 2002-2005; 1936 messages; approximately XXXX (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0002, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
    Email messages require additional screening. Contact research services for more information
    Includes email messages in PST format, as well as a copy migrated into MBOX format.
  - General SMMS email messages, 2005-2011; 1091 messages; approximately 145 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0002, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
    Includes email messages in EML format, as well as a copy migrated into MBOX format.
  - Opening SMMS email messages, 2009-2011; 772 messages; approximately 100 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0002, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - Governing Council SMMS email messages, 2009-2011; 293 messages; approximately 50 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0002, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - Operational SMMS email messages, 2008-2011; 146 messages; approximately 5 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0002, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - Land and Building SMMS email messages, 2007-2011; 1682 messages; approximately 525 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0002, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - USA SMMS email messages, 2008; 42 messages; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0002, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - Pictures SMMS email messages, 2011; 2 messages; approximately 10 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0002, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - Governing Council Executive SMMS email messages, 2009-2011; 55 messages; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0002, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - Legal Section 21 198a LD SMMS email messages, 2007-2011; 185 messages; approximately 25 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0002, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - Search SMMS email messages, 2008-2011; 223 messages; approximately 5 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0002, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - Communication and Promotion SMMS email messages, 2009-2011; 184 messages; approximately 225 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0002, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - Naming of Spaces SMMS email messages, 2009-2010; 74 messages; approximately 20 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0002, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - Student Life SMMS email messages, 2007-2008; 9 messages; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0002, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - Commission on Theological Education SMMS email messages, 2004-2007; 61 messages; approximately 2 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0002, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - Funding SMMS email messages, 2007-2011; 1198 messages; approximately 180 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0002, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - Academics EMMU SMMS email messages, 2007-2011; 122 messages, approximately 10 megabytes. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0002, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)
  - Faculty SMMS email messages, 2008-2011; 24 messages; less than 1 megabyte. (Digital-materials RL01260-SET-0002, Disk RL01260-USB-0001)